[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Subtitles in the making and will be available soon]
Mom.
I haven't heard from anyone yet.
Yes.
I think it's hard to find a buyer
to find a buyer.
Yes.
That's good.
Because
I think we should keep collecting rent for now.
What do you think, Mom?
Really?
You think so too?
Hello?
Turn on the speaker.
Okay.
I'm hanging up, mom.
Are you trying to fool me?
Why do you want to hear my mom's voice so much?
I just want to hear her voice.
I haven't seen her for a long time.
I want to know how she's doing
how she's doing.
Marrying a bad man like your dad
who married your dad.
Why are you suddenly scolding my dad?
Why? Can't I?
You don't have to scold him.
What? What do you want?
Come on, kick me. Come on.
Kick me!
Kick me.
I can't touch your ghost.
Come on.
Well...
What?
This one Dobby
What are you doing?
This is my memorial tablet.
Do you want to destroy my memorial tablet?
It’s too easy for you to destroy it.
People like you should be like this.
Like this.
Look.
Look, it's diaphragmatic now.
This isn't enough.
Oh, this isn't good.
Okay.
Look. Hey.
What are you doing here?
Oh.
I'm just wiping grandpa's tablet
and clean it.
By the way, what's the matter?
I sent you the list of tenants
from the North. You're teasing me again.
But there's something I don't understand.
Why do we have to select the people from the North?
Because back then,
Grandma Gaysson and grandpa
wanted to escape to Chiang Mai.
so I thought it'd be better to start from the North.
Okay. I see.
You're so smart.
But your dad takes after you.
Which tenant should we start with?
You know this place best.
Of course.
Find someone who's the easiest to cooperate with us.
You're leaving the job to me, aren't you?
Am I wrong?
You know them all. I just know them.
That makes sense. Yes.
I think he's simple and cute.
He'll be fine. He'll be easy to talk.
Mr Dew.
Are you in your room? This is Dannis.
Yes.
Hold on.
[Dew] [Professional: University student]
Well...
Miss Dannis, what can I do for you?
I have something to ask you, Mr Dew.
Do you have a relative
a female relative called Gaysson?
is about 70 years old.
Yes.
My grandma's name is Gaysson.
Really?
God is on my side.
I found her first.
Why do you ask my grandma?
Is something wrong?
My grandpa
has been looking for a friend named Gaysson.
Your grandma's name is Gaysson, right?
Yes.
Maybe she’s my grandpa’s friend.
Can you show us her photo?
I remember there was.
we took a photo together on our birthday.
Great.
Why don't you come in first?
I need to look for it.
Okay. Sure.
Come in.
Can this room really go in?
Hey, go inside.
They invited us. What?
Do you want to come in?
Okay, I'll come in. Come in.
Please come in.
Okay.
[UFO]
♪ Dormitory D ♪
Every step we take is meaningful
There is no path that is worthless
As long as our hearts keep searching
♪I will find it someday♪
It's good to travel alone But isn't it better to have you by my side?
With your help on the journey I won't be lonely anymore
♪ It's as if true love is still waiting in dorm D
As if this love has always been there waiting in this dorm
Maybe there will be beautiful true love
leaving touching stories on every step along the way ♪
Maybe it's not a coincidence
Let us meet here
In the road ahead
There might be some special meaning ♪
Maybe because of Dorm D
that made me meet you today
[Dormitory D]
Please sit on the sofa and wait.
Okay.
Hey.
Be careful not to crush Paul.
Paul?
Where is Paul?
Please move.
This is Paul.
From Paul's movie, 2011. [Note: Paul] in Paul's movie.
The comedy that aliens escaped from Zone 51.
I even have a CD.
Do you want to see it?
Uh. Uh.
Forget about Paul.
Now show us
the photo of Grandma Gaysson. Yes.
Okay.
Hold on.
Paul.
Sit here.
Let them sit together.
OK.
Please sit down.
Paul, let's sit together.
Bobby,
He doesn't even have a picture of anyone
All aliens and UFO.
I don't think
have such a crazy grandson.
I found it.
Goodness. Here.
It's been a while.
Your face turned green.
I miss you so much.
Oh no.
Mr Dew.
Do you have any other photos of Grandma Gaysson?
This is the only photo I took with my grandma.
After that birthday,
since that birthday.
What about the others?
Have you taken photos of your grandma?
Like your mother.
Has she taken a photo with your grandma?
I'll try to call my mom.
But I don't know if she'll pick up.
Thank you, Mr Dew.
Yes, thank you.
Hello?
What? Dew is cute and cooperative.
Isn't he a bit abnormal?
He's wearing something sharp on his ears.
You. What?
Lower your voice.
Don't let Paul hear you.
Paul, keep it a secret.
What?
Why are you like him?
Believe it or not,
Dew will tell us when he comes back.
Grandma Gaysoon's photo is on Planet Namekian.
And we have to ride Piccolo there. [Note: Piccolo is Dragon Ball.] and see her photos
to see her photos.
Do you believe it?
Wait and see. Should we go?
What?
If you think I'm crazy,
then leave.
I don't think I can help you.
What? Please.
Mr Dew, calm down.
Don’t mind him.
He's so mean and rude.
What's wrong with him? Please.
Please leave.
Paul doesn't want you to stay here anymore.
Paul, did you tell on me?
Paul?
Go out.
Don't pressure Paul.
Let's go.
We haven't got anything yet.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
[Do-MUN-DRIP]
Young man,
a cup of orange coffee.
Do you want
Thai honey orange or ordinary orange?
Honey orange.
Are they from Chiang Mai
or Qinglai?
Chiang Mai?
Do you want Fang County
or Mae AI?
Mae AI.
Should I be a little shy or shy? [Note: Mae] AI's AI's Thai is "Shy".
Why do you have so many questions?
Don't be shy.
How about a bold one?
Listen to me.
I want Mai. Orange coffee from AI County.
Wait.
Okay.
That's all?
Fang County's products are fine too.
Oranges are fine, anywhere is fine.
All oranges are gone.
Only coconut left.
Are you kidding me?
Calm down.
Calm down. I'm sorry.
I think everyone in TikTok likes this joke.
I just want to make friends with you.
I don't think you can make friends like this.
You might get beaten up.
Then give me two cups of latte.
Let's go.
I don't feel anything when I look at others.
Why do you look like that
the owner of the cafe?
I should ask AI.
When I look at someone,
when I look at someone?
Is something wrong with my eyes?
Your eyesight is fine.
The reason why it feels like this
because the brain will temporarily block everything around you
to capture every detail of the person who attracts you.
You can also say that he caught you.
Come on.
Why are you fishing?
I'm not a fish.
If you want to check,
you can try to get close to him and smell his scent.
If you feel relaxed
when you smell it,
Then he is
the person you've been looking for.
Okay.
Wow.
20 baht cash, sir.
Well...
Why did you call him 20 baht cash?
Oh.
He paid me 20 baht for the chicken.
Oh. Oh.
My name is Drip.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Dolly.
How do I smell it to be natural?
Forget it.
Hello, bro.
Dolly.
Oh, my.
Come here.
What are you doing?
What did I tell you?
You can't even get close to them.
Why didn't you tell me you wanted coffee?
I can make it for you.
Come on, Dolly.
Mom.
Don't hang out with anyone from that cafe.
I just wanted a cup of coffee.
You said you had a lot of customers.
Why didn't I see anything?
Not yet.
What?
Look.
DaWin has calculated it for me.
I'll be rich at 4 p.m.
and my business will be good.
Pack the table.
My treat.
Take it as the roast chicken you treated me before.
Now.
Here's your chance.
Thanks, bro.
Hey, Mom.
Go back to your shop after the coffee is done.
I don't want to see you.
It's annoying.
Let's go.
Don't rush me.
People nearby said Aunt Duang's restaurant
is the best here.
Which dish is your specialty?
Give me one.
Mom.
It's 4 p.m.
He might be your money.
Have a seat.
What do you want to eat?
Check the menu.
Order whatever you want.
Thank you.
We must verify it this time.
Here's the ice.
Goodness.
Excuse me.
Can you tell fortune here?
[Fortune-telling]
Then tell my fortune.
I've never been a fortune teller.
There must be a next time when there is a first time.
If you want a peaceful life,
let the tarot cards show you the way.
What do you want?
How about a cafe?
and see if it will be popular in the future.
It doesn't matter.
Just let it be.
See?
You're just like your dad
Just like your dad.
That's why I don't like him.
Let's call it a relationship.
Fine.
I've never been in a relationship.
I also want to know if I'm lucky in love.
Now!
Good.
DaWin is very accurate.
I can finally smell it.
Mom.
My nose is going to break.
What are you cooking?
Can we verify it today?
Can you think before you talk?
What are you doing?
Can't you just shut the door? Okay.
You've been scolding me all the way.
Take a breath and continue.
and then scold me.
Can you stop scolding me?
You have to admit it.
Dew is a weirdo.
You should ask someone else for help. No.
His grandma is Gaysson.
Maybe she's the Gaysson we're looking for.
Yes.
What do you want me to do?
As you can see,
Dew kicked us out of the room.
In my opinion,
we should find an alien to talk to him.
Nonsense.
Where can we find aliens?
There are.
I do know someone
He knows a lot about aliens.
In a movie called MiB,
in a movie called MiB.
Is it "The Man in Black"? It's "MEN". In Black.
It's called "MAMEWIN BAN". Moo.
It's about an alien called Mamew.
broke into Ban Moo and robbed the circuit board to repair the airship.
I can't wait to see
I want to see what the investor looks like.
By the way,
the same person as I thought?
Wow.
Look at your smile.
Why do I suddenly have a bad feeling?
Well,
I've never won a lottery.
I was right this time.
I'm leaving.
Is your friend really reliable?
When he played Bang Raman,
his beard was crooked.
It's still stuck on my eyes.
Hey!
Don't underestimate him.
You know
how serious his acting is.
Dax.
Are you ready to transform into a man in black
and become an alien?
I'm always ready.
What?
I promise I'll be perfect.
Dax. What?
What happened to your tongue?
I fell down the stairs.
I bit my tongue.
What?
I fell down the stairs and bit my tongue.
Can you be more specific?
I'm going.
Go up the stairs.
I slipped and bit my tongue.
It hurts.
It's nothing. Goodness.
Forget it.
He can't even speak clearly now.
How can he communicate with Dew?
What should we do?
Hey, don't worry.
Leave everything to me.
Huh?
I have an idea.
What?
Gosh.
What the heck?
Oh.
Don't worry.
Hey! Hey.
Are you Spider-Man?
Hey.
Don't... Don't worry.
I have an idea.
Yes. Oh.
What's the way, Dax? Yes.
Every time I see him smile like that, I have a bad feeling.
Why are you here again?
I'm here to apologize, bro.
Are you mocking me again?
I'm not here to laugh at you.
Actually, we are the same kind of people.
I like aliens too.
I used to be laughed at
That's why I pretended to hate these things.
If you really like aliens,
tell me what it is.
What are stars?
Stars are
an alien soul that was born in human mother's womb.
An alien?
Oh my. Hey.
Make it clear.
Give it to me.
How is it?
You don't know
The species
the alien soul
by human mother
is also known as
seed from the stars.
Then why is 69
the symbol of aliens?
This is a trap question.
Because the numbers of aliens
are actually 1
and 7.
is your room number.
Welcome.
Let's go inside. Okay.
We have a lot to talk about.
Please come in. Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
What?
Hey
That's right
[1%]
Shut up.
I'm so happy
I'm so happy to have friends to talk about this.
Yes.
Let's name our Universe Union.
What should we call it?
You're Dobby.
I'm Dew.
Let’s call it
Dobby Dew Star Alliance.
The symbol will be pointed at the starry sky
to point at the starry sky.
Ah oh
Like this. How?
You point to the stars.
Like this?
I'm receiving energy from the stars.
See? Do I have to stick my face this close?
Go that way.
You pointed at the wrong direction.
OK.
Keep this posture.
Like this.
Good. I like this symbol.
Um, Dew.
I think...
we should stop forming an alliance.
It's just the two of us now.
with just the two of us.
Right.
It's not the time
to name the Alliance.
Because tonight,
we have an important meeting with IZ.
IZ?
Yes.
Are you talking about "One Pot"? [Note: IZ homophonic joke]
One, one, one.
Right?
Stop it.
Goodness.
You're quite good at joking.
I mean Comet IZ878.
will pass by Earth tonight.
Oh, right. Okay.
Let's pack up.
Don't be late.
Okay.
What should I bring?
Wait.
My mom called me.
Okay.
Mom.
You suddenly texted Line about something urgent.
Mom, do you have a photo of your grandma?
I want one.
Gaysson.
We finally meet.
And then?
I just want it.
Is this an emergency?
You scared me.
I thought you were in trouble
to clean up the mess.
Don't call me again
don't call me again.
You're wasting my time.
What?
That's my mom.
Let's go.
Let's go now.
or we won't be able to see the comet.
Okay.
What do you want?
You take the chair. Okay.
I'll take the camera.
Hey.
This way.
Hello? Okay.
What about Gaysson's photo?
Let's go. My photo.
You can't see it every day. Hey, where are you going?
Aunt Duang, you're so good at cooking.
Every dish is delicious.
Just throw it away.
The shrimp meat tastes very good.
and tender.
and bouncy.
Besides, the sauce
is full of tongue.
The aroma of the spice is full of the mouth.
It's like a vanilla garden.
Are you praising me or talking nonsense?
Mom.
It's just a normal dump.
He praised me like Chef Pom's cooking. It's really good.
It's really delicious.
I've never had such delicious food in my life.
Does he live in Yangsan?
He hasn't even eaten a normal dump.
Mom,
Don't say that.
Mr. Drip, after dinner,
we can continue our fortune-telling.
Goodness. Hey.
My mom's spanking
You're bleeding from sneezing.
I sneezed when I was washing my hands.
and my face hit the sink.
Can you keep counting for me?
Maybe another day.
I'm fine.
I've been through a lot like this.
You wanted me to calculate your relationship, right?
Yes.
Don't find this fortune teller.
Unless you want to lose the one you love.
When will you let it go?
I don't want to argue with you anymore.
I won't let it go.
I'll expose you
and expose all the things you did
until you stop deceiving people.
Enough.
It's been so long.
Give me your hand.
Shake hands and make up.
Ouch!
It hurts.
Do you want to fight?
Mom.
Mom, look at them.
It doesn't look like they're making up.
I think they're going to fight.
Wait.
Let go! Hey!
If you don't let go,
I'll chop off your arms and legs.
and make soup.
Mr Drip.
I won't give it to you today.
I'm not in the mood.
What?
Oh my.
Wait!
Drip.
You'd better ask someone else to eat with you.
I'm not in the mood either.
What is this?
What's going on?
Why do they hate each other so much?
I don't know the whole story.
I only know a little.
Hey.
Although she said that,
but she knows everything.
She can't wait
to tell the truth.
Dolly, I’m your mom.
Do you want to hear it?
See?
Hey.
Mom, go ahead.
I want to hear it.
This happened two years ago.
You ordered everything.
Just 200 baht.
Here.
You're doing well.
Buy girls shrimps and seafood if you have money.
I'm just asking.
When can you tell me
where my girlfriend lives?
What girlfriend?
We're just...
We're still checking each other's hearts.
What era is this?
If you like her, talk to her.
There's no need to check.
I want to talk to her too.
But...
She wants to graduate first.
Oh, I see.
I want you to admit that I'm your boyfriend.
We walk side by side and say goodbye. Good night.
Do you like my style?
Please let me walk into your heart.
Do you want a fortune teller?
Hello?
She didn't want to talk to you
because she's two-timing you.
Thank you for your concern.
But...
I trust her.
She's a good person.
She will never cheat on you.
Good luck.
I want you to admit that I'm your boyfriend.
People in love
are surrounded by pink bubbles.
Auntie, do you want to feel pink bubbles again?
Can I take a look?
Will your husband come back?
Hey.
Are you going to make tarot money at my store?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
My bag is old.
Can you take me to buy a new one, honey?
Of course, honey.
Hey! Hello?
Ma'am.
No need to hide.
I saw everything.
By the way,
Who's NOKNINK?
She's my guest.
She came to see me as a fortune teller.
And she seems to like me.
Really?
She lives here too.
Do you have her photo?
I don't think it's a good idea.
I wanted to show it to you too.
She's pretty cute.
Your food is here.
What's wrong?
My mom's 5,000 baht debt.
I can't get the money to pay the debt for her.
I'm so stressed out, honey.
Goodness.
What a good boy.
There should be more than 5,000 baht here.
Oh, but take it.
When you have money,
when you have money.
Crab.
It's amazing.
It's obviously a love triangle.
When did Master Dang and DaWin
knew they were chasing the same girl?
Three...
Three days?
Two, one, zero. Time's up.
Wait.
Have a seat.
If you want to know the follow-up,
order something first.
Let's continue.
But...
There's still a full table left.
So what?
Okay, I'll order.
Anything. One more.
Please wait a moment.
Okay.
All right.
It's time to confirm
if he's the person I'm looking for.
Mr. Drip.
Did you drop something?
Let me see.
Mom.
Why is it so choking every day?
[Dorm D]
It's sunny today.
We will definitely see IZ Comet.
Yes.
I don't want to see IZ comet.
I want to see Gaysson's picture more.
and ask him
if he can call his mother again.
I want to know about Gaysson.
My heart
is melting.
Soft and gentle.
Soft, gentle, gentle.
I'll ask you later.
Wow.
Maoxing Group can see it clearly.
You know
the Thai version, right?
Maoxing Group?
Yes.
Hahaha.
What is that?
Found it.
The Seven Sisters Star Group.
Maoxing Group is also known as the Seven Sisters.
I'm speechless.
Miss Dannis,
You should go to the bathroom now.
Subaru.
Star.
A group.
Legend of adults. [Note: In Thai] "Maoxing Group" sounds similar to "Lord".
Huh?
Maoxing Group.
Legend of Chick. [Note:] [The pronunciation of Thai is similar.]
Legend of Chick?
You really don't know?
or are you kidding me?
Oh, actually...
Chicken Planet.
Gugu.
Like a chick, why...
I don't understand.
Why are you still talking? Chick.
I'll do it myself.
I don't know what's hard. Gugu.
Chicken Planet?
Yes.
I was just kidding.
Little Rooster.
Gugu.
You must be joking.
Yes.
Have you ever thought
why those chicks
follow the hen into the fire?
Even a hen is willing to sacrifice her life to support a monk.
Maybe she's worried that the monk lacks protein.
This is called filial piety.
Others may think
the chicks are filial to the hen.
But personally,
because the chicks love the hen deeply,
so they don’t want to live
without a hen.
I think so too.
Sometimes I envy those chicks
They love each other
and share weal and woe.
I also hope
in my house.
Unfortunately,
my family is not on this planet.
So the person who just called you
wasn't your real mom?
I was born with her belly
Do you remember what I asked you about the species?
Yes
Maybe I'm one of them
a thread of soul from the alien
born in this world.
Why do you think so?
If I were her child,
she wouldn't treat me as an extra.
That's why I like stargazing.
I hope one day
my family can come from a planet
and bring me home with UFO.
I will.
Hello.
Grandpa, what’s wrong?
I pity him.
My family abandoned him.
Just like me,
We were abandoned by each other's family.
You are the one who abandoned our family.
We never abandoned you.
Goodness.
Why do you look so pitiful?
Gosh.
Mr Dobby. What?
Someone on X said they saw IZ Comet.
But its coordinates have changed.
Really?
Hello?
Mr Dew, be careful.
I sail like this just to find...
Hey!
Please be gentle.
It suddenly stopped.
I fell to death.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm burning up.
Thank you for being my weightlifter.
I really can't find a big rubber tire.
You're welcome.
I'm here. Okay.
Sorry, I'm exhausted.
I can help anytime.
As a good citizen,
as a good citizen.
By the way,
Why did you raise your hand
when the police salute?
If you raise your hand above your head,
like this.
You're good.
Didn't you just say you're exhausted?
What fell?
What?
107.
This is the key to Mr Dew's room.
Why is it here?
Mr. Dollar. Mr Dew wants to jump off the building.
What should we do?
Hurry up.
Do you have his information?
I'll contact his family to comfort him.
Yes, it's in my office.
I'll get it.
Guard.
There's an emergency in Dorm D.
The Thai spicy stir-fry
is ready.
Here.
Dolly, what’s wrong?
I’m washing my nose, mom.
It's all because of you.
I don't know what I'm cooking every day.
I can't smell anything now.
So I cook every day.
What's there to complain about?
What?
Let's continue
the love triangle between Master Dang and Dawei.
Please.
Master Dang didn't know
he didn't know
was in a relationship with her.
Until...
you shouldn't have confessed to her.
What?
These three cards show
you'll be cheated by her.
If you fall in love with her,
your life will be a mess.
Are you sure?
Tarot cards are like this.
Believe it or not depends on you.
That's all I can do.
Take your girlfriend
to change your fate with me.
This temple is having an event.
Buy one free.
Soak it in herbal water to get rid of bad luck.
I'm looking for someone to bid with me.
Mr DaWin, can you take a look?
I think I saw it wrongly.
Can we talk tomorrow?
Unfortunately, I have something to do today.
I have to go.
If you don't like herbs,
you can sleep in the coffin to repel evil and change your fate.
Many people will go.
I'm not lying.
It's okay.
Goodness.
Wait.
Well...
When he saw it with his own eyes,
a reliable friend
whom he trusted
became his sworn enemy.
Open the door!
You fortune teller!
What brings you here?
Why do you want to fight with me?
How dare you ask me?
You pretended to read my fortune
and told me not to talk to NOKNINK.
It's all for yourself, right?
Huh?
For what?
Nankik is my girlfriend.
What girlfriend?
I've asked her.
She said she's single.
I've been chasing her for a long time.
Wait.
The person you talked about last time...
NOKNINK?
So...
she lied to us at the same time.
Don't change the subject.
Just say it
just say it.
I'm not making excuses or fighting with you.
That's what tarot cards say.
She fooled me too.
Don't frame her, okay?
You like to steal what others love, right?
Then I'll show you
how it feels to lose something you love.
Hey.
Put it down.
Hello?
Hey!
Give it to me.
My card.
DaWin, what happened?
Sorry to bother you.
Damn maintenance!
Since then,
everyone knows
Nankiki
is scarier than ghosts.
She lied to everyone.
Especially all the men in this dorm.
Fortunately,
Dollar and Dolly were not cheated by her.
How could Dollar be cheated by her, Mom?
He always
always runs around the dorm
running around the dorm with tires.
Really?
Why didn't you stop him?
How could I stop him?
He forced me to run away.
Now that we know the real identity of NOKNINK,
why is Master Dang still mad at DaWin?
DaWin helped him so much. I don't want him to be cheated.
For someone with prejudice,
even if it's over,
he refused to let it go.
And they even kissed.
It's getting worse
the situation gets worse.
DaWin was angry too.
Master Dang was angry at his cards.
I don't know much.
Do you really not know
Or do you want me to order more?
Enough.
Stop ordering anything.
My nose can't take it anymore.
But to be honest, I can understand him.
Although it was an accident,
I was kissed for no reason.
and being attacked like this.
If it were me, I would be angry too.
What do you think, bro?
Luckily,
If I really made a mistake,
he wouldn't want to see my face now.
I’d better keep a distance from him.
Mr. Dolly, what's wrong?
Well...
Nothing.
I'm fine.
That's good.
Bill, please.
Please calculate the money for me.
Copy that.
Hello? Goodness.
Goodness. Auntie!
Ma'am.
Are you okay?
Even he and mom
are slow in my eyes.
Ah!
I've had enough.
What's wrong with him?
He ran away when Mom was about to fall.
Dolly!
Mr Dobby
Why are people standing downstairs?
I don't know what they are looking at.
Or are they just like us
just like us?
Look.
Oh.
I don't think so.
There are police cars
and ambulance.
Did something happen down there?
Dew.
What are you doing?
What happened?
Why is everyone here?
What? Dew wants to jump off the building.
No, it's a misunderstanding.
Mr. Dew didn't jump off the building. Yes.
Really?
What's going on, Dew?
Nothing, Mom.
Or are you playing
to attract people's attention?
No, he just...
He's not trying to jump off a building.
What? What?
He's just going to see the comet.
The comet is...
Comet?
Gosh.
What are you talking about?
Ma'am, calm down.
Calm down, okay?
What happened, Dew?
So you didn’t want to kill yourself, right?
I don't have time
to clean up your mess.
If I had known this,
I should have sent you to your father.
He should be
with his new family.
I have my own family to take care of.
Isn't Dew your family?
Forget it, Mr Dobby.
It's no use talking.
No matter what,
in her eyes.
I'm not her chick,
She's not my hen either.
If only it was the UFO who came to pick me up.
Hey, Dew.
Hello? Hey.
Mr Dew. Dobby.
Dobby.
Dobaby
Dobby, are you okay?
You must be fine
What should I do
what should I do?
Hello.
Grandpa, are you worried
no one will help you find Grandma Gayshin?
You're fine.
Mr Dew.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Goodness.
Hey, don't move.
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
How is it?
Are you okay? Gosh.
It was so loud. Are you hurt?
Do you need an ambulance?
Is your bone okay? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Does your leg hurt? What?
It's so scary.
Goodness.
One by one.
You...
Yes.
Where?
I...
Hurt?
Is it?
Where?
Does it hurt?
Is it?
Hello? Are you hurt?
That's not what I meant.
Mr Dew, are you okay?
Dew.
Are you crazy?
How long are you going to
my life?
Hey.
If you still know your place as a mother,
you shouldn't have said that.
It sounds nice.
Who are you?
None of your business.
He's my son.
I can scold him however I want.
What is a mother? It's not just words.
I should acknowledge it from the bottom of my heart.
Dew.
Your friend is really good.
How dare you
but you didn't stop it?
You idiot.
He scolded me like that.
but you still sit there in peace.
If he wants to die,
just let him be.
Don't contact me again.
Calm down, ma'am.
I can't believe
There's such a mother in this world.
What? What?
I can't believe
There's such a mother in this world.
What? What?
Forget it.
He said, "Forget it."
How did you understand that?
It's more clear.
Ask me.
"Kid, are you okay?"
Is it that hard?
Why can't my mom say it?
Maybe I was right.
I'm not a human on this planet.
What a pity.
I should disappear with that comet.
Mr Dew.
You don't have to move to another planet.
Even if your mother doesn't love you,
it doesn't mean
no one loves you.
The meaning of "family"
doesn't mean
who gave birth to us.
We can define our own family.
Look around you.
There are so many people who love and care about you.
You don't have to chase the hen and jump into the fire.
You can go with other chicks.
Gugu.
Puppy.
Woof.
Kitty.
Meow.
Little frog.
Crack.
or Buffalo. [Note: Buffalo in Thai says he's stupid.]
That's enough.
This is enough to comfort people.
See?
You have a warm family, Mr Dew. Yes.
Thank you.
Seeing everyone hugging Dew,
I want to hug you too, Dobby.
Let me hug you.
I want to feel
the warmth of my dear grandson.
Dobby.
Let me hug you.
I...
Don't cry, Mr Dew.
I support you.
I...
We're all here, Mr Dew. Yes.
I can't breathe.
There might be a beautiful true love
Ah Really?
Why didn't you tell me at first?
♪ Every step along the way leaving a moving story ♪ ♪
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry.
Uh...
Thank you very much.
Maybe it's not a coincidence
Our encounter seems
Let us meet here
His ears are dropping It's not this way, right?
[In the next episode]
Wait.
It's not eyelashes.
What? What?
Take it off. What?
One, two. Hello?
Where is Dome?
Din!
Hey, stop it.
They're fighting again.
When will you
stop?
No way. No.
What's going on?
Let go of me! Oh.
♪ Dormitory D ♪
Every step we take is meaningful
There is no path that is worthless
As long as our hearts keep searching
♪I will find it someday♪
It's good to travel alone But isn't it better to have you by my side?
With your help on the journey I won't be lonely anymore
♪ It's as if true love is still waiting in dorm D
As if this love has always been there waiting in this dorm
Maybe there will be beautiful true love
leaving touching stories on every step along the way ♪
Maybe it's not a coincidence
Let us meet here
In the road ahead
There might be some special meaning ♪
Maybe because of Dorm D
that made me meet you today
[Dorm D]